<entries>
<entry name="WiseSaying109">What is done out of love always takes place beyond good and evil. - Friedrich Nietzsche</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying1">Everyone has talent. What is rare is the courage to follow the talent to the dark place where it leads. - Erica Jong</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying2">The pride of youth is in strength and beauty, the pride of old age is in discretion. - Democritus</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying3">Genius has electric power which earth can never tame. - Lydia M. Child</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying4">Great ability develops and reveals itself increasingly with every new assignment. - Baltasar Gracian</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying5">Ability is of little account without opportunity. - Napoleon Bonaparte</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying41">The future, according to some scientists, will be exactly like the past, only far more expensive. - John Sladek</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying42">You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying43">I tend to live in the past because most of my life is there. - Herb Caen</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying44">Life wouldn&apos;t be worth living if I worried over the future as well as the present. - William Somerset Maugham</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying45">Let no one ever come to you without leaving better and happier. - Mother Teresa</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying46">Only in the agony of parting do we look into the depths of love. - George Eliot</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying47">Man&apos;s feelings are always purest and most glowing in the hour of meeting and of farewell. - Jean Paul Richter</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying48">Where is human nature so weak as in the bookstore? - Henry Ward Beecher</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying49">You can cover a great deal of country in books. - Andrew Lang</entry>
<entry name="achievement10">&quot;Guts and tenacity&quot; Try the same stage 10 Times</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying6">Genius may have its limitations, but stupidity is not thus handicapped. - Elbert Hubbard</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying50">People say that life is the thing, but I prefer reading. - Logan Pearsall Smith</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying51">Just the knowledge that a good book is awaiting one at the end of a long day makes that day happier. - Kathleen Norris</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying52">Outside of a dog, a book is man&apos;s best friend. Inside of a dog it&apos;s too dark to read. - Groucho Marx</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying53">Always read stuff that will make you look good if you die in the middle of it. - P. J. O&apos;Rourke</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying54">Wear the old coat and buy the new book. - Austin Phelps</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying55">The multitude of books is making us ignorant. - Voltaire</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying56">Woe be to him that reads but one book. - George Herbert</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying57">The reading of all good books is like a conversation with the finest men of past centuries. - Rene Descartes</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying58">There is no mistaking a real book when one meets it. It is like falling in love. - Christopher Morley</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying59">Read much, but not many books. - Benjamin Franklin</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying94">Life is what happens to you while you&apos;re busy making other plans. - John Lennon</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying95">You can only be young once. But you can always be immature. - Dave Barry</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying96">Life is not fair; get used to it. - Bill Gates</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying60">Live always in the best company when you read. - Sydney Smith</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying61">Nothing changes your opinion of a friend so surely as success - yours or his. - Franklin P. Jones</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying62">The friendship that can cease has never been real. - Saint Jerome</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying63">Friends may come and go, but enemies accumulate. - Thomas Jones</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying64">The ornament of a house is the friends who frequent it. - Ralph Waldo Emerson</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying65">Be slow in choosing a friend, slower in changing. - Benjamin Franklin</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying66">Friendship make prosperity more shining and lessens adversity by dividing and sharing it. - Cicero</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying67">Talent wins games, but teamwork wins championships. - Michael Jordan</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying68">Misfortune shows those who are not really friends. - Aristotle</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying69">Nothing&apos;s better than the wind to your back, the sun in front of you, and your friends beside you. - Aaron Douglas Trimble</entry>
<entry name="achievement7">&quot;Advanced worker bee&quot; Gain 150 Star</entry>
<entry name="achievement8">&quot;Professional worker bee&quot; Gain 240 Star</entry>
<entry name="achievement9">&quot;Challenger&quot; Try the same stage 5 Times</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying12">Life is a risk. - Diane Frolov</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying40">If you don&apos;t find God in the next person you meet, it is a waste of time looking for him further. - Mahatma Gandhi</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying70">A friend is a second self. - Aristotle</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying71">Your happiness is defined by what makes your spirit sing. - Nancy Sullivan</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying72">No great man ever complains of want of opportunity. - Ralph Waldo Emerson</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying73">The moment of victory is much too short to live for that and nothing else. - Martina Navratilova</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying74">Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it. - Henry David Thoreau</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying75">You always pass failure on the way to success. - Mickey Rooney</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying76">Men are not prisoners of fate, but only prisoners of their own minds. - Franklin D. Roosevelt</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying77">Success is the ability to go from one failure to another with no loss of enthusiasm. - Sir Winston Churchill</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying78">The strongest of all warriors are these two -- Time and Patience. - Leo Tolstoy</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying79">One of the greatest victories you can gain over someone is to beat him at politeness. - Josh Billings</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying97">A man has to have a code, a way of life to live by. - John Wayne</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying98">Maturity is only a short break in adolescence. - Jules Feiffer</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying99">Life is far too important a thing ever to talk seriously about. - Oscar Wilde</entry>
<entry name="achievement11">&quot;Don&apos;t give up!&quot; Try the same stage 20 Times</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying80">Success isn&apos;t permanent, and failure isn&apos;t fatal. - Mike Ditka</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying81">While we stop to think, we often miss our opportunity. - Publilius Syrus</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying82">Luck is the residue of design. - Branch Rickey</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying83">The most potent muse of all is our own inner child. - Stephen Nachmanovitch</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying84">If you can concentrate always on the present, you&apos;ll be a happy man. - Paulo Cuelho</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying85">Education&apos;s purpose is to replace an empty mind with an open one. - Malcolm Forbes</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying86">It is possible to store the mind with a million facts and still be entirely uneducated. - Alec Bourne</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying87">The great aim of education is not knowledge but action - Herbert Spencer</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying88">Whoever ceases to be a student has never been a student. - George Iles</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying89">Education begins a gentleman, conversation completes him. - Thomas Fuller</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying93">Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving. - Albert Einstein</entry>
<entry name="achievement1">&quot;Welcome!&quot; First time of game access</entry>
<entry name="achievement2">&quot;Come on in &quot; connect game 10 times</entry>
<entry name="achievement3">&quot;I&apos;ve been waiting for you :)&quot; connect game 30 times</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying90">He who can, does. He who cannot, teaches. - George Bernard Shaw</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying91">Not the senses I have but what I do with them is my kingdom. - Helen Keller</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying92">The tragedy of life is what dies in the hearts and souls of people while they live. - Albert Einstein</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying10">The journey is the reward. - Steve Jobs</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying11">Well begun is half done. - Aristotle</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying39">If we take care of the moments, the years will take care of themselves.</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying13">Rather be dead than cool. - Kurt Cobain</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying14">Everything in your world is created by what you think. - Oprah Winfrey</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying15">Appetite, with an opinion of attaining, is called hope; the same, without such opinion, despair. - Thomas Hobbes</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying16">Fear cannot be without hope nor hope without fear. - Baruch Spinoza</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying17">What we dwell on is who we become. - Oprah Winfrey</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying18">Perpetual optimism is a force multiplier. - Colin Powell</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying19">To want to be what one can be is purpose in life. - Cynthia Ozick</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying20">There is nothing like dream to create the future. Utopia to-day, flesh and blood tomorrow. - Victor Hugo</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying21">He who has never hoped can never despair. - George Bernard Shaw</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying22">He that lives upon hope will die fasting. - Benjamin Franklin</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying23">Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence. - Helen Keller</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying24">Total absence of humor renders life impossible. - Colette</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying25">Laughter is inner jogging. - Norman Cousins</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying26">For the things we have to learn before we can do them, we learn by doing them. - Aristotle</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying27">Idleness is not doing nothing. Idleness is being free to do anything. - Floyd Dell</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying28">Try not to become a man of success but rather try to become a man of value. - Albert Einstein</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying29">In preparing for battle I have always found that plans are useless, but planning is indispensable. - Dwight D. Eisenhower</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying30">Happiness lies in the joy of achievement and the thrill of creative effort. - Franklin D. Roosevelt</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying31">What is written without effort is in general read without pleasure. - Samuel Johnson</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying32">God doesn&apos;t require us to succeed; he only requires that you try. - Mother Teresa</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying33">You need chaos in your soul to give birth to a dancing star. - Friedrich Nietzsche</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying34">If I only had an hour to chop down a tree, I would spend the first 45 minutes sharpening my axe. - Abraham Lincoln</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying35">If you judge people, you have no time to love them. - Mother Teresa</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying36">The trouble with our times is that the future is not what it used to be. - Paul Valery</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying37">I wasted time, and now doth time waste me. - William Shakespeare</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying38">I never think of the future - it comes soon enough.</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying7">I think the prime reason for existence, for living in this world, is discovery. - James Dean</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying8">First weigh the considerations, then take the risks. - Helmuth von Moltke</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying9">Don&apos;t be afraid your life will end; be afraid that it will never begin. - Grace Hansen</entry>
<entry name="achievement4">&quot;Now I know!&quot; Gain 10 Star</entry>
<entry name="achievement5">&quot;Beginner worker bee&quot; Gain 30 Star</entry>
<entry name="achievement6">&quot;Intermediate worker bee&quot; Gain 90 Star</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying100">Is virtue a thing remote? I wish to be virtuous, and lo! Virtue is at hand. - Confucius</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying101">The secret of eternal youth is arrested development. - Alice Roosevelt Longworth</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying102">Everything that I understand, I understand only because I love. - Leo Tolstoy</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying103">Love is, above all else, the gift of oneself. - Jean Anouilh</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying104">Love is a gross exaggeration of the difference between one person and everyone else. - William Shakespeare</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying105">There is no remedy for love but to love more. - Henry David Thoreau</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying106">Life&apos;s greatest happiness is to be convinced we are loved. - Victor Hugo</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying107">Tis the most tender part of love, each other to forgive. - John Sheffield</entry>
<entry name="WiseSaying108">All love that has not friendship for its base, is like a mansion built upon sand. - Ella Wheeler Wilcox</entry>
</entries>
